I sneak up close to you
then tap your shoulder — tap!
the look on your surprised face—
I can't get over how cute you are.
on tiptoe, I tap the neon
and sparks of light jump up and dance.
today I feel extra playful
only with you, again and again.
when your gaze follows me
my heart goes "pop-pop" and leaps.
almost caught, almost gone
should I run away for a sec…?
(but you'll catch me in no time.)
when I hop along in front of you
you come closer smiling, don't you?
as I twirl through neon light
you reach out and call my name.
I'm only teasing a little
so why does my heart flutter this much.
every time I see you
little hearts go "pop-pop," bursting out.
close to your arms
when I catch your eye
the moment you smile
the world turns pink.
behind loose strands of hair
your fingertips almost brush mine…
that feeling makes
my cheeks grow warm again.
it's okay to come a little closer.
today I just feel like teasing.
when you smile
I end up smiling too…
(this isn't a secret, right?)
when I hop along in front of you
you come closer smiling, don't you?
as I twirl through neon light
you reach out and call my name.
it was only a little tease
but when you hold me, I melt.
every time you're near
my heart goes "pop-pop-pop" and dances.
should I run away? no—catch me.
just kidding… but I mean it.
seeing your smiling face
makes me want to act cute again.
when I run through the light
you hold me like you've been waiting for me.
the two of us beneath tonight's neon—
our little game, just for two.
light footsteps, a fluttering heart
I bounce up again when I see you.
by your side again today
my heart goes "pop!" and bursts out.